Thank you for watching!
You keep me going too.
Hello! Stay, this time with Waka Matsumoto of Angulum and
and Yuhane Yamazaki from Beyonce's Tenshukawa Net.
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with us until the end.
Hello Project 2023 Summer City Circuit has just started!
Yes, the first day of the Beyons concert started at Kitakyushu Soleil Hall the other day!
And Angulum's first day will be on the 22nd at the Orix Theatre.
What do you think will be the difference from the spring tour this time as an encore?
Yes, well, Beyoncé performed at Nippon Budokan for the second time in May.
Based on that performance, the Beyoncé has become even more united.
I think we will be able to show you a neo Beyons.
Yes, that's right.
And two new members, Yukiho and Hana Goto, have joined our group.
I hope to show you the new Angeleum with a new structure.
Yes.
By the way, it's almost time for students to take their summer vacation, which makes me very happy.
By the way, if you could have a summer vacation, what would you like to do?
I haven't been to the beach with everyone in Angulum yet. Before I joined the group, it seems that all the Angulum members used to go to the beach together, so I'd love to go and have a barbecue with everyone.
I'd love to go and have a barbecue or something with everyone. Sounds fun.
I'm a mountain climber. I think it's tiring, but I think it gives you a sense of accomplishment.
If I get some time off, I'd like to do some serious mountain climbing.
We have a lot of summer tours coming up, so I'm going to do my best.
We have a lot of summer tours coming up, so we'll do our best.
Are you still up for it? You're not slacking off, are you?
Don't blink!
Louder than you've ever screamed before.
Okay, now, just change it up a little bit and yell it four times.
You ready?
Here we go.
One, two, one, two, three, four.
Jump up!
Well, that's not good enough.
I don't care about the last glance.
Next, let's split up and play left and right!
This one first!Let's start with this one!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Chake up! Chake up! Chake up! Chake up!
Yeah!
Nice left! Yeah! Right is losing!
Here we go!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Chake up! Chake up! Chake up! Chake up!
Whoo!
Let's go for the last time with the whole audience!
One, two, three, four.
Jump up!
Jump up! Jump up!
All together!
Jump up!
OK, Yokohama, keep up the momentum!
You usually have a pretty face
But in my heart, I hate it... even though I'm a sucker for words.
I love words, but I can't say what I really feel
But I can't say what I really feel
You're right, I'm not reliable.
You're cute most of the time, but it's a bore.
Come on, let me see your face today.
Make me swoon.
I like it when you do.
My mind is made up.
But, oh, tonight...
I'll be the one to do it.
I'm not a girl from a girl.
My love is not to be taken lightly.
I won't be ego-driven.
If you're going to do this, do it cool.
When the time comes, that's when it's all going to come down to the wire.
I'll see you tonight.
Good night.Good night.
Great! Great! Great! Great!
If you take my love lightly
I'm not gonna let you down a little bit.
If you're gonna cheat on me, be cool about it
When push comes to shove
When you're dreaming, that's when it counts
Tonight I'll give you a good night's sleep
And a good night to you.
I'm sure it's going to work out
Beyonz Amemorigawa Umi no Yamazaki Yuhane sends you Halo! Sta.
Okay, from here I'd like to tell you a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you a few questions.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo.
I'll do my best.
Please do.
Please tell us the key to today's hair arrangement.
I curled it loosely with a thick iron.
It's cute!
What is the point of today's fashion?
Yes, it's summer, so it's fresh.
I was a guest performer at the M-Line Special 2023 Magical Wish held on the 25th of last month.
What did you notice on stage with your seniors?
Eh, rhythm
Please tell me how to cope with the heat I would like to ask you, Mr. Yamazaki
Eat ice cream
What is your ambition for Beyons this summer?
Have more people play Beyoncé to more people
Thank you very much.
Yes, yes, I was talking about the rhythm at the M-Line last month.
I was able to stand on stage with the senior members of Hello Project.
I sang a lot of Hello Project songs that weren't Beyoncé songs.
So I could feel 16 beats in many of the songs.
I had to pay attention to the rhythm and sing beautifully so that the songs wouldn't be too slow.
It really brought back what I had learned when I was a trainee member of Halo Pro.It really brought back to me what I had learned when I was a trainee at Halo Pro.
It made me want to work even harder.
Yes, I also listened to the song by S/mileage at Takeuchi-san's graduation performance the other day, and I really felt that I could relate to it.
I also felt the same way when Takeuchi-san said something about more rhythm in her song at her graduation performance the other day.
Yes, that's right.
I think 16 beats are important.
And I wanted to ask you about your measures against the heat.
Yes, eating ice cream.
When it gets hot, I want to eat ice cream.
It makes me happy and cools me down.
Yes, that's right.
Please do eat ice cream.
Yes, I want to eat a lot of ice cream this year.
Questions for Wakana Matsumoto will be asked after the VTR.
Hello! Stay!
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't.
I won't kiss you okay
Even you couldn't take it away from me
CHOOSE CHOOSE PRIDE BRIDE NOW ON SALE
Oh Let's Play Lovely Music
Let's Dance Disco till morning Let's
CHOOSE CHOOSE FUNKY FLASHING NOW ON SALE
Is it because of summer, or is it a dream?
Ocha no Ma Yurashiki Full
Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer July 26th release
Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha Matcha
Zocha Zocha Zocha Zocha Zocha Zocha Zocha Mahoroba
Tea Horse Tea Horse Tea Horse Mahoroba Koinoba
Showa and 2025 both on sale July 26
Shaylena: The Power of Believing in Yourself
Ordinary, but forbidden, unbroken
Ochanoma New single Chikenare July 26th release
Yoridorimidori midorimidori, I can't choose just one, Tezuki Meijer
Pampaka-pan all over the world Before that
Ochanoma New Single Yoridorimidori July 26th release
Halo! Ste.Hallo! STE.
Next, I would like to ask Wakana Matsumoto a question.
Yes, I will answer.
Yes, please.
Wakana Matsumoto says her hobby is taking a walk these days.
What do you do when you go for a walk in this hot season?
Wearing a parasol
How nice!
It's been about two months since a new member joined the group.
How do you feel about having a junior member younger than you?
They are just so cute!
So cute!
What are you working on to improve your skills?
Practicing my curly hair.
How do you speak so well?
Talk a lot.
Oh!
We're entering the second half of 2023.
What would you like to accomplish in the second half of this year?
To go out with two new members
Oh!
Yes, thank you.
I'd like to talk about something that's been bothering me.
I wanted to ask you, "How can you speak so well? You're such a good talker, Kazunade.
Thank you very much, but I love to talk a lot.
Even at home, I talk a lot with my family, and in Angeleum, both senior and junior members talk a lot.
So I think I have a lot of communication with them.
Then, I'd like to talk a lot with Kazunade-chan, too.
Yes, by all means.
I'm sure your skills will improve, so please talk with us.
And, yes, it's only been about two months since a new member joined the group, and you have a junior member who's younger than you.
That's right. You've got a new member.
Yes, Goto Hana is one year younger than me, and Yoshimoto Yukiha is one year older.
This is the first time we have a younger member.
I hope we can get to know each other better and better.
I'm looking forward to seeing them.I'm looking forward to seeing it.
We will continue after this. Stay tuned for more after this!
Sound Hodori 🐯 Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이
Sound Hodori on Instagram & Twitter
Clearly water death from here.
Why, I'm hungry.
I just slept until late afternoon
Why do I have tears in my eyes?
My precious life.
I should be dead all the time.
Oh, greatness. The world is about to get a surprise.
What is this?
I wish I could challenge someone's heart like you.
I'll give it to you. I'm in the mood. I can do something.
Let's think in fantasy.
Hey!
Hey! Something something something something
Nothing, nothing, something, no idea
How about this then?
This piano is so original!
Hey! Where is it, where is it, where is it, where is it, where is the idea?
You already have one.
It's inside you.
Really?
Life is an art form.
Follow me!
Yeah.
The mundane, the mundane, the mundane.
Closing with a glass tile.
The final explosion.
A brief blink of an eye.
Break the silence.
With a big, booming firework.
I'm gonna get some more sleep first.
Hey, what's going on?
Senpai!Senpai!
I need to sleep.
Senpai!
I haven't even left the house yet.
No, no, no.
I don't get it.
Failure!
I'm gonna miss you.
Fail!
It's been a long time.
We'll face each other with gusto.
We'll part with a smile.
In the meantime
We'll go back to the great days of our senior year.
Barrier forum
Still the same as it was when you lived
So many changed egos and mouths
I'm counting and I'm sleepy
Strange!
Hey, that's
It's something to try to hear
As for heartlessness
We're all in this together!
Life is an art form.
It's always been a revolution
With only the mundane
We just laugh
Love is a Makuhari
After the sadness
The great end fine
Boom, boom, boom, call the past
What a lie to you
Hero of Love
Forever
Hero of love
BornBorn.
Everyone's first life
Each etude
Play it beautifully
Music is a giant
Aimed at our thoughts
I want to.
Love, pride, empathy
I can finally go beyond.
There are only a few things in life
The impulses that go on and on
I don't love you.
Stressful.
Youth is an explosion... A single moment...
I lived the moments that mattered.
I was gently held, I laughed, I laughed, I laughed...
Jopan Senpai
Jopan.
Thank you for watching.
Next is a presentation of lyrics that have touched my heart.
Are there any lyrics or phrases that have been popping into your head recently?
I'm thinking of Beyonce's song "In the night sky where you can't even draw a dream.
There is a lyric in the song "You and I are sharing a song, it's a miracle" by Beyonce.
When I first heard the song and saw the lyrics
I thought it was a wonderful phrase.
I treasure this song very much.
I think it is a very beautiful lyric.
What do you think?
I, Matsumoto, like the lyrics of the song "Tomoyo" by Angelem.
There is a lyric, "It's not goodbye, it's so bye-bye" in the song "Tomoyo" by Angeleum.
This song "Tomoyo" is often sung at graduation concerts.
Graduation is a very sad time, isn't it?
I think it's a very warm lyric because it feels closer to "bye-bye" than "good-bye.
I think the lyrics are very warm.
It's really nice. It's really good.
Please watch the VTR. Please watch the VTR.Now please watch the VTR. Go ahead!
Presentation of lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of the songs of Hello!
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Nanami Kubota, will be presenting.
Here it is.
It's a song by Juice-Juice called "Ganbattei Naiyo! by Juice-Juice,
It's about how you can't cheat yourself with cheap self-praise, and how you want to have real self-confidence,
I originally really loved this song by Juice-Juice, "I can't go on! I used to really love this song by Juice-Juice,
I heard this song when I was a trainee member of the Halo Pro trainee unit and dreamed of making my debut,
There are times when you feel like you are going to give up,
I listened to this song and thought it was a song that made me feel like I could do my best at those times,
When you are lacking in confidence, you may feel like you are gaining confidence by rewarding yourself, for example, by putting on makeup,
You put on lipstick or something like that,
But I want to have real confidence,
I want to have the ability to perform, and I want to have the confidence that comes with making a debut,
I really love the way she expresses her true feelings of wanting that kind of confidence,
I really love this song.
It's great.
When you lose confidence, you don't know what to do to get around, don't you?
When you listen to this song at that time, it permeates you with an aha feeling.
I think that's really wonderful.
I totally understand.
The title of the song is "I can't do my best," but this song is about wanting to do your best, isn't it?
So I felt that this song pushes you to do your best.
Yes, it is a very good song. It is a very good song, so if you ever feel like you can't do your best, please listen to it,
Please give it a listen.
Please look forward to the next installment!
Hello! STE!
with Yuka Matsumoto of Angelem,
Yuka Matsumoto of Angulum and Yuhane Yamazaki of Beyonce Amamori Kawami will be presenting the next installment of "Halo! Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year.
Project's 25th anniversary this year,
Project's 25th anniversary this year, we would like to introduce to you a music video with a cute set that we have selected from the songs of the Project's 25 years.
Yes, I'm Matsumoto.
I, Matsumoto, would like to introduce you first.Yes, then I, Matsumoto, would like to introduce myself first.
Yes, I am Ugi Ugi Love from Country Girls.
I am Ugi Ugi Love from Country Girls.
Oh, wow!
The set of the music video for this song is a bit American and retro,
It's cute.
I think it's a very nice music video, and the cuteness of the members really stands out.
Yes, I think it's a great music video.
In the middle of the floor.
With a pony that stands out too much
Come and get me at the wind-breaking cheapo.
Ikkasu yo todakidatta.
Maybe it's your first love, Homitan
Hold me close, Fall in love
You can call me Maria.
I care about you from this day forward.
It's the future of my uncle's life
I'm a man and a woman, and we always meet out of the blue, so it's very important.
I'm wondering if today might be the day.
I've already got eye balls.
I hope you meet Dave Freres tonight.
I'm making adult, or I'd have asked him to the dance.
Oh, my heart.
Boogie boogie boogie boogie.
Boogie boogie boogie.
Hallo! Hello!
Now, I, Yamazaki, choose the music video with the cute set!
℃-ute's "The happiest girl in the world"!
The set is like a room in the members' colors.
The costumes that ℃-ute is wearing are also colorful with the members' colors.
This music video will make you happy just by looking at it!
The big sky taught me
What I have to do now
Anyway, since I was born a girl
Only I can do it
I want to fall in loveI want to fall in love.
I dreamed of it when I was a little girl.
I dreamed of being a kindergarten teacher.
I chose a slightly different career path
I've always wanted to be a neighbor's brother.
My mom said he's getting married soon to someone really beautiful.
Who's going to get married soon to a very beautiful woman.
Life is changing day by day
I've got to do something about it, life
Wow wow yeah yeah
Girls are strange
A little dangerous love
I'm living in search of
Wow wow yeah yeah
I'm just being honest
I love you a little
I don't know how I'm gonna get close to him
I don't want to lose
I'm the happiest guy in the world
Hey, Rapson
That's what I'm talking about.
Hello! Ste.
Fresh dreams this and that
Always freshly sparkled
Believe and you'll be fine
I've tried both sweet and sour
Infinity
With a tinker's switch
A new Oliver
Surprisingly OK
Kibatz idea
Stand by for tomorrow
Bye bye
full of dreams
more and more and more and more and moreSo many to choose from, so many to choose from, so many to choose from
I want to choose and decide I want to be thrilled by all of them
Pan-pan-pan throughout society
But first, I've got to get my hands on some bread
Aim, and you'll get the foot
Tea cups
There's so many to choose from
I'm sure they won't choose one.
I'm sure you won't choose one.
more and more this romance
from now on, stutter, stutter, stutter
Let's make it all come true
You idiot!
Stop sending the game
Kaki?
Yes, Kimi.
It's been a long time.
I hear you, I write, I hear you.
Mellow out, mellow out, mellow out
I'm full of dreams
Alone
I don't deny who I am
I'm planning a strong future
I'm gonna be brave, I'm gonna be brave, I'm gonna be brave
It's my time
Because it's small
So many more, so many more, so many more
I can't hide it, I know it's gonna be my mate
Like this, like this, like this, like this, like this
You got a friend, Gan!
Let's dance like senseis.
It's so good!
So many, many, many, many, many, many, many, many
Pull the antlers, pull the antlers, pull the antlers...
Next, "clang, clang, clang, clang.
I'm so excited, I can't believe it.I'm so excited!
I could do anything.
A water source of dreams as sweet as a peach A strawberry, a single layer of tiny peaches
Just once, or many, or a lot, a lot, Brock!
Ocha-no-Ma, Terranda, Wan-num, Haina Paul.
Wherever you are, Go Go Go, go Go!
You deliver, Wi-Fi of energy
Straight to regret, no today
My journey may be long
I'll take a break, it's non-negotiable
Ah! Here I go!
Dreams, just in time for the fight
So many choices, so many choices, so many choices
I can't choose just one, they're all so exciting
Pang, pang, pang, pang, pang, pang, pang, pang, pang, pang, pang...
Aim and you'll get it.
I'm so cool!
So many choices, so many choices, so many choices
I'm not going to choose one. I'll be a monorama when I find out.
I'll be a monorama when I find out. I'll be a monorama now.
Pearl, please.
I can't reach it! I can't get out of the way!
I'm almost there! Fight!
With Yuka Matsumoto of Angulum,
Beyonce, Ami Amamorikawa, and Yuhane Yamazaki of Halo! Stay!
It's time to say goodbye!
Here's an announcement!
Hello Project 2023 Summer City Circuit has started!
Angelem will be performing at the Orix Theatre in Osaka on July 22nd.
Beyonce will be performing at the Orix Theater on the 23rd.
If you are in the area, please come and see us!
Please come and see us if you are in the area!
We will do our best so that you can see us improved from the spring tour.
And on August 13th, Angelem will be performing at the Rock in Japan Festival 2023!
This time, we will be the top performer on the Glass Stage.
This will be my second festival in the Rockies.This will be my second Rocky festival.
I hope to give a passionate performance.
Beyonce will be performing at Tokyo Idol Festival 2023 on August 4th and 5th.
On the 4th, we will be performing at the Amemurokawa Sea Seasonings Subway.
And on the 5th, we will be performing as Beyonce!
It's really rare to perform as a unit, so I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all, and I'm sure you'll be able to see many different Beyoncé performances.
The stage is a part of the Hello! Project members will appear on the channel every week.
Project members every Wednesday, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time we have Waka Matsumoto of Angulum and Beyonce Amamurokawa Umi of Beyonce.
Beyonce, and Yuhane Yamazaki of Amamurokawaumi.
Good bye.
This is Yuhane Yamazaki from Beyonce.